

INAYATULLAH

Pesh Imam

C

+92 3443864956



Date of Birth 09-01-1985



House no. 52 Shah Baharo Street Paro Gajanpur Larkana

EXPERTISE

- Hifz-e-Quran
- Islamic Studies
- Arabic Studies

LANGUAGE

- Sindhi
- Urdu

INTEREST & HOBBIES

- Reading newspaper
- Teaching
- Delivering Islamic Lectures

PROFILE

Dedicated and knowledgeable Pesh Imam with a strong background in Islamic studies, particularly in Hifz-e-Quran, and expertise in Islamic teachings and Arabic studies. With over 20 years of experience at the Executive Engineer Works Office, I bring a blend of religious guidance and practical organizational skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Executive Engineer Works Office

2004-present

Pesh Imam

Jamia Masjid Noor Mustafa

2010-present

Dars-e-Quran

EDUCATION

BA 2012-2014

Jamia Anwar-e-Mustafa Sukkur

Intermediate HSC-II 2009-2011

Sachal Sarmat ORT: College Larkana

Matriculation SSC-II 2004-2006

Sachal Sarmat ORT: College Larkana

ACHIEVEMENTS

• Hafiz-e-Quran